<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Huddled Masses (Site News)</title><link>http://blog.HuddledMasses.org/</link><description></description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 12:34:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>http://getnikola.com/</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Missing Content</title><link>http://blog.HuddledMasses.org/missing-content/</link><dc:creator>Joel "Jaykul" Bennett</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;Since I've blown away all my old blog content, there are a lot of pages missing that were really useful.
I'm going to bring the best of them back, and I have plans to actually rewrite some of the older ones to update them
(part of the reason I let the old ones go is that some of them were so out-of-date that they might have been misleading).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there is one or more of my old articles in particular that you'd like to see come back, please post a comment below!&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>Site News</category><guid>http://blog.HuddledMasses.org/missing-content/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 03:28:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Fresh Start</title><link>http://blog.HuddledMasses.org/a-fresh-start/</link><dc:creator>Joel "Jaykul" Bennett</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago, someone somehow injected a shell onto my WordPress powered blog site. They managed to get multiple hacking tools installed, delete files required for hosting, and who knows what else. Needless to say I was frustrated and upset. In fact, I was so frustrated that to get rid of it I just tore down the whole site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I apologize for all the hundreds of broken links that are pointed at my domain right now. I have a database backup, but I want to try a few other blogging tools out, and I am not sure I can trust the downloads or even images on the old site -- I don't want to restore all the posts &lt;em&gt;and then&lt;/em&gt; find out the downloads are infected or the images have been replaced. Furthermore, when I stood up a new WordPress site, it did not perform well on my DreamHost server, and I started to wonder if I needed new hosting or new blogging tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- TEASER_END --&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="a-state-of-flux"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A state of flux&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, to try switching to a static site generator instead of a server-side blogging tool, so I went to &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.staticgen.com/"&gt;StaticGen&lt;/a&gt; and I've started working my way through some of the many interesting options.  I'll probably be switching back and forth between them over the coming days, so the site may change quite a bit (not just visually, but in permalinks, etc.) until I settle on one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also decided that I will not restore the database backup and deal with cleaning all the downloads that have accumulated in the last ... almost 20 years of blogging (isn't that crazy?).  Instead,  I will start over. I can still restore individual articles from my old blog by hand (at least the ones that people really are still looking for), and that will give me the chance to update the content and to convert them to markdown (yeah, I think textile lost that battle).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please &lt;a href="http://blog.HuddledMasses.org/a-fresh-start/#id1"&gt;&lt;span class="problematic" id="id2"&gt;:doc:`let me know &amp;lt;missing-content&amp;gt;`_&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; when you hit a missing page that you want back, and I'll move that up my priority list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="system-message" id="id1"&gt;
&lt;p class="system-message-title"&gt;System Message: WARNING/2 (&lt;tt class="docutils"&gt;&amp;lt;string&amp;gt;&lt;/tt&gt;, line 14); &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://blog.HuddledMasses.org/a-fresh-start/#id2"&gt;backlink&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
Mismatch: both interpreted text role prefix and reference suffix.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Site News</category><guid>http://blog.HuddledMasses.org/a-fresh-start/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 05:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>About Huddled Masses</title><link>http://blog.HuddledMasses.org/about-huddled-masses/</link><dc:creator>Joel "Jaykul" Bennett</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;This is web site is dedicated to the musings of Joel Bennett (aka Jaykul) about technology, software, software development, the web, and the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any resemblance of the views expressed and the views of my employer, my terminal, or the view out my window are purely coincidental. The resemblance between them and my own views is non-deterministic. The question of the existence of views in the absence of anyone to hold them is left as an exercise for the reader.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="the-man-of-many-hats"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The Man of Many Hats&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;div class="line-block"&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Not like the giant companies of great fame,&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;With componentized factories cranking out clones;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Here on our white-washed pages shall stand&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;A solitary man with a keyboard whose products&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Are the collected sparks, and his name:&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;The DevOps King.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="attribution"&gt;—Joel Bennett&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With apologies to Emma Lazarus:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="the-new-colossus"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The New Colossus&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;div class="line-block"&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Not like the brazen giant of Greek fame,&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;With conquering limbs astride from land to land;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Here at our sea-washed, sunset gates shall stand&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;A mighty woman with a torch, whose flame&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Is the imprisoned lightning, and her name&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Mother of Exiles. From her beacon-hand&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Glows world-wide welcome; her mild eyes command&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;The air-bridged harbor that twin cities frame.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;"Keep ancient lands, your storied pomp!" cries she&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;With silent lips. "Give me your tired, your poor,&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Your huddled masses yearning to breathe free,&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;The wretched refuse of your teeming shore.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;Send these, the homeless, tempest-tost to me,&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="line"&gt;I lift my lamp beside the golden door!"&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="attribution"&gt;—Emma Lazarus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please Note:&lt;/strong&gt; I occasionally link to things I think are great. When I do, I occasionally find a "referral code" so I can make a little cash. I promise that I don't link to anything just because of the cash (I wouldn't cross the street for the amount of cash those links bring in, never mind write a whole blog post), and I promise I won't let anyone buy links in my blog content ... but I do not promise that things I link to will stay great as time passes, nor that you will agree with me about their greatness!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>Site News</category><guid>http://blog.HuddledMasses.org/about-huddled-masses/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 05:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>